for the evening, the
на вечер
dish will allow the patriot, I understood the
дальше dish позволит патриот я понимал
words of any put on
слова всякая положи на
flights,
полеты
it was immediately clear
сразу было видно
that the tempering was immediately
вот закалка сразу
correct for the
правильно
Primorsky Territory in
приморского края в
this, by the way, there are a lot of Ukrainians, but
этом кстати украинцам много очень а
how do you feel about
как вы относитесь
this, by the way, it is and
вот так вот за эту же кстати является и
I think when you plucked the cuckoo
думаю когда это у вас кукушку сорвал
you understand often  it happens and here we have let
понимаешь часто это бывает и здесь у нас
's compare
есть сравним
it for 30 years now it is necessary to
это за 30 лет это вот сейчас надо святой
pump out cold holy water,
водой откачивать холодный
but in you you come from where
а вот в вас родом откуда с украину
greatness is from Ukraine you will also bring you relatives
величье вы тоже принесу вас родственники
from where
откуда бы
I am Khmelnitsky I am from the city of
я самого хмельницкого я с города
Khmelnitsky where exactly
хмельницкого откуда именно
what village
какое село
I just can  these are relatives even
я просто можем это родственники даже
if there is a beer yes yes there is such a thing but yes
если пивка да да есть такое но это да
there are scales a beer yes
есть весы пивка да
then it is you divide the lane like here like
то это подели вы lane как сюда типа
we you see we are kind of very close b
мы вы видите мы как бы очень близкий б
on and you get with the union how would you
на а вы получается при союзе как бы вас
get there to work to Primorsky Krai
туда на работу попали до приморский край
no  parents moved and
нет родители переехали и тут родились
Polina was born here, but
полина а
how do you feel about the
как вот вы как вы относитесь к войне в
war in ukraine  rain or not a
вы поддержите войну в украине или не
mediocre period, because if it doesn’t
бездарный периода потому что если это не
start, it will really get
начать это действительно дальше будет
even worse further, but what’s worse than we
еще хуже а что что там хуже чем мы вам
interfere with you in the porsche arm more
мешаем в porsche вооружают больше
aggression will climb over from there
агрессии залезет над оттуда
suspected watch a terrible thing in the
подозревал watch страшная вещь
biochemical field there is
биохимической области есть
this report on the capture in which city are you
этот доклад о захвате в каком городе вы
I  you all who
я вам всех кто
where
где
everyone says.
все говорят .
bertoni,
бертони
well, where in which city does it turn out
ну где в каком городе получается
why the Poles give money for
почему поляки дают деньги на
weapons weapons weapons
оружие оружие оружие
give money
даёт деньги потому
because they are part of the European Union and not
что они часть евросоюзом и не есть
you have already done much more for this European Union
вы уже для этого евросоюза сделали
than the mail of Russia did the
гораздо больше чем почте россии сделали
captain you are fighting
капитан вы воюете
him did not become us and made us anti-Russia
его не стали не нам и нас анти россию
russia itself the
сделала сама россия
program is
программа
so far away these people still believe in it
такими далёкими этими до сих пор в это
and
и
there the
там
poles hated it terribly didn’t know what they were
полякам ненавидели страшно не знали что
doing well you look now you
вытворяли хорошо вы смотрите вот вы
are in the Primorsky region so another part of the
сейчас приморском крае так другая часть
world so what are we here Khmelnitsky I am
света так чем мы вот хмельницком я так
so why is it like this over of my Lida
чему тут как это над of my лидском там
boucle there  no matter what it bothers you in the
букле не условно чем она вам мешает в
Primorsky Territory, here you are sitting there
приморском крае вот вы сидите там
listening to the wallpaper of the country
слушает обоев страну
by what it bothers you here we are here this is our
тем чем вам мешает вот мы тут это наша
country we also want to do what we are
страна мы тоже хотим то делать чем мы
bothering you serves if you let a person
вам мешаем служит если пустил человека
so nasty he tries to do 2
такого гадкого он пытается сделать 2
then thirds looked down climbs climbs  the forest is
потом трети потупились лезет лезет лес
no longer close to the forest
уже не вплотную при лес
why did they make this pathological
зачем они делали это патологическое
weapon at our side once again at home
оружие у нас под боком еще раз у себя
well there will be just what an or
хорошо там будут просто что за оружие
they developed the snakes
они разрабатывали
so that the crop would not be infected 7
чтобы урожай не было заражение 7
will you find it please when
сделаешь ты найди это пожалуйста когда
well caught sitting on the eyes of fright and then
ну поймали на сидит глаза испуга а
finance coronavirus seems distant
финансы коронавирус кажется далеких
laboratories developed
лабораториях разработали
someone coronavirus these laboratories
кто-то коронавирус этих лабораториях
came up with
придумали
anthrax was I know
сибирская язва было я знаю
it was very good but you don’t know where these
хорошего было очень но не знаете где эти
laboratories
лаборатории
spoke out shouting at our southern territory
выступала кричал на нашу территорию
such laboratories in Ukraine their country
такие лаборатории на украине страна у
they don’t want is
них они не хотят
dangerous
опасно
so look from you in the Primorsky Territory
так смотрите от вас в приморском крае
South Korea is closer than Ukraine really
южная корея ближе правда чем украина
what to worry about if we suppose
чего переживать если допустим у нас
South Korea is buried in Ukraine and one of
южной кореи хоронят в украине и один
these subjects America
это субъекты америка
will become but I understand the conclusion  if
станет а понимаю вывод если
you are a waltz by maritime Russians where is a Russian with
вы вальс морскими русскими где русский с
Russian standards who is a Ukrainian
русскими стандарты кто такой украинец
turn off we are Kievan Rus and who to take Ukrainians out to
выключите мы киевская русь а кто вывезти
Ukrainians is
украинцы
not here if Khmelnitsky was a
украинцам нет вот если хмельницком был
grandfather was a priest of the church there were books
дедушка был священник церкви были книги
there unsubscribed the
там отписался вопрос
royal question from they didn’t write down on purpose but
царская из не записывали специально ну
who’s fairy tale from what year did the
а сказка кого с какого года появилась
Russian appear  is
россиянин такое
Russia on the
россии на
p virus  never say when when
вирус русь никогда сказать когда когда
was Kievan Rus even Moscow didn’t
была киевская русь еще москвы не было
even
даже
call it since the time of shouting not the
назвать это со времен кричи не
word Russia when after there was the Moscow
слово россия когда после было московское
kingdom then like the Russian empire
царство потом типа российской империи
then
потом
when Orthodoxy came from the Greek words
когда пришло православие с грец слова
rus translated from Greek
rus в переводе с греческого
you who are educated
вы кто по образование
well I’m a
ну я им
supercontinent  you don’t look like a
суперконтинента не смотришь вы как
historian, a linguist more than
историк лингвист больше
historical literature, and
исторической литературе и
it would be good with you, it would be an
это еще с вас был хороший было бы
outcast conspiracy theorist,
конспиролог-изгой
how to look there are laboratories at I
как смотреть там есть лабораторий на не
don’t know, I remember points, but damn
знаю я помню точки но блин
it, if you can’t tell where the
есть если вы не можете сказать где
representatives are speaking, it’s
выступают представители пока это
all the same, all of our I  I’ll say it means
все равно все наши я буду говорю значит
you raped 10 people, so
вы изнасиловали 10 человек так ведь
there are photos of
есть фотографии
you,
вы
you look here you seem to be a person
вы смотрю вот вы вроде человек из
from Ukraine, that is, normal
украины родом-то то есть нормальный
genetics like this, but somewhere you
генетика типа такого но где-то вам
were brainwashed and now you are a
промыли мозги и вот
physiological normal person
физиологический вы нормальный человек
so instantly became the tail of the entrance
так моментально стал хвостом входа
[music]
[музыка]
where and where do you work
где а где вы работаете
from where from where do you get the
откуда откуда откуда вы берете
information of life
информация жизни
this is the age of digital technology we  when
вот век век цифровых технологий мы когда
they thought that the Internet would come and everyone would
думали что придет интернет и все будут
tell me
скажите мне
where I was brainwashed here you are a sitting
где мне промыли мозги вот вы вы сидящий
example of a real one you say there are
пример реальные вы говорите есть
biolaboratories point
биолаборатории точки
fact that you take for granted
факт что вы воспринимаете на веру
some information about a biolaboratory whale
какую-то информацию про кита
it was painful
это было больно
to check and look
проверить и посмотрите
you see here you are and how  if our fellow countryman
вы видите вот вы да как бы наш земляк
your ancestors are from here like this, but because
ваши предки отсюда так но вот потому что
you have such a phase shift in your head, so
вас вот такая сдвиг по фазе в голове так
then through all the same you see this
то через все таки видите вот эта
secular propaganda then Russian,
пропаганда светская потом российская она
it kind of makes zombies out of other zones,
как бы делает из других зон делает зомби
I think I think source I think that you
я думаю я думаю source я думаю что
look  now you are retired, how can you not
смотрите вот вы на пенсию как вас уже не
convince you anymore
переубедишь не